<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lee Trout</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Lee Trout</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 14:18:21 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Episode Zero</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e0/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 14:27:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e0/</guid>
      <description>Episode Zero is the preview of what is to come in the Fish Tales podcast.
I explain some of the motivations for starting the show and give credit to my inspiration and those who have helped me.
I am excited to share the stories I&amp;rsquo;ve gathered and I hope you stick around and tune to enjoy them!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ange Yaghi &amp; Engine Simulator</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 14:27:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e1/</guid>
      <description>In this episode we explore Ange&amp;rsquo;s background, how he got started programming and how the engine simulator came about. Of particular interest to me was how it went viral and the pressures that surfaced. This episode kicked off the podcast recording in late 2022 and I really cannot thank Ange enough for investing the time to record with me with no idea what this podcast is or would be or when it would even be published.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greg Marlow &amp; Computer Animation</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2023 13:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e2/</guid>
      <description>Greg is a long time friend, first time caller and he&amp;rsquo;s here to tell us about his career and the work he has done in 3D animation. He tells us all about working on AAA titles including Civilization V and how he transitioned to teaching at ETSU. I am certain you can&amp;rsquo;t make it through this episode without laughing and smiling as you listen to Greg tell his entertaining and interesting stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Andrew Welch: Hosting podcasts and working in tech</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e3/</guid>
      <description> Andrew Welch is a developer and the host of devMode.fm, a podcast dedicated to modern web development. He&amp;rsquo;s been working in technology for years and we explored his experience working in development and transitioning over to training.
Andrew was instrumental in launching Fish Tales so once again, thank you Andrew!
Links from the show:
https://devmode.fm https://nystudio107.com/ https://craftcms.com/ MacOS 7/8 emulation https://microconf.com/ https://www.startupsfortherestofus.com/ </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leslie Kiszka &amp; Food Blogging</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e4/</guid>
      <description>Leslie Kiszka is on the show to talk about running her food blog StressBaking.com! We had a great chat and she was patient enough to walk me through all the various aspects of her blog including the origin story and what she has to do to keep things running. It was a blast to learn about it and hear it all directly from her!
Links from the show:
Baking Basics How to calibrate your oven B.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Haroun Serang: Music Production, coding &amp; philosophy</title>
      <link>/fishtales/e5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Mar 2023 10:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/fishtales/e5/</guid>
      <description>Haroun is a principal software engineer and sound engineer. We had a great chat about his background in sound engineering and some of the artists he&amp;rsquo;s worked with over the years before diving into our opinions on various aspects of software engineering. Haroun is one of those people that will always leave you wanting to learn more as he has such a broad knowledge base that covers so many topics.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
